<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tony&#39;s Blog for Data Science</title>
    <link>https://yiplf.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tony&#39;s Blog for Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yiplf.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Real Estate Price Prediction</title>
      <link>https://yiplf.github.io/blog/project-real-estate-price-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yiplf.github.io/blog/project-real-estate-price-prediction/</guid>
      <description> Price Appraisal is an essential part of the real estate market.
In this project, I used a real estate dataset compiled by others(from Kaggle) to train classification models.
The models can be deployed to predict the sale price of a specific property given various features.
Click on this page for modeling process in Python.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Customer Churn Prediction</title>
      <link>https://yiplf.github.io/blog/project-customer-churn-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yiplf.github.io/blog/project-customer-churn-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Customer Turnover (or Churn) is an popular topic for subscription-based industries (e.g. T-Mobile, Netflix), particularly in telecommunications.
In this project, I used a dataset from a fictional telco company (from Kaggle &amp;amp; IBM) to train classification models.
The models can be deployed to determine whether a customer is likely to churn based on the probability assigned by the model to each customer in the dataset.
Click on this page for the modeling process in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://yiplf.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yiplf.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me
Hi, My name is Tony Yip, an aspiring Data Scientist with two years of industry experience as an Data/BI Analyst. I have an academic background in Business Administration, concentrating in Business Analytics and Decision-Making, Management Information Systems, and Operations Management.
Work/Industry Experience
I worked as a Data Analyst in a special trackwork manufacturing company. Throughout my career, I have supported the cause of inventory and manufacturing optimization through the creation of Power BI Dashboards, design and documentation of internal control processes, and hosting of meetings with production planners and managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://yiplf.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yiplf.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
